{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "Pragmatists were hardly the first men _________ beliefs control behavior.",
            "a": "insist",
            "b": "insisted",
            "c": "who insists",
            "d": "to insist",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- The next/ the first/ the second/ the last/ the only/ the best....+ To Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He asked me if John had the capability ___.",
            "a": "to do that",
            "b": "to doing",
            "c": "doing that",
            "d": "do that",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Have capabiltiy to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Inland canals are used ___ farm and factory goods to nearby towns or seaports.",
            "a": "shipping",
            "b": "to shipping",
            "c": "to ship",
            "d": "in shipping",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- Get/be used to + Verb_ing: Be familar with doing something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am free _________ I did not quite know the sort of creature I had to deal with.",
            "a": "to confess",
            "b": "confessing",
            "c": "confess",
            "d": "in confessing",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Be/feel free to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wasn't ___six miles every day.",
            "a": "strong enough to walk",
            "b": "enough strong for walking",
            "c": "enough strong to walk",
            "d": "strong enough for walking",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Be + adj + strong + enough to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "___ , my tennis went daily from bad to worse, and the worse it became, the more I loved it.",
            "a": "To honest be",
            "b": "If I be honest",
            "c": "To be quite honest",
            "d": "Being honest",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "\n- To be quite honest: used when you tell someone what you really think ",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "After studying hard to become an accountant, he discovered that it was not what he wanted ___.",
            "a": "to do",
            "b": "that",
            "c": "doing",
            "d": "to",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "\n- Want + To Verb, in this sentence Verb can be hidden\n",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I muttered encouraging words to myself ___ up my courage.",
            "a": "to keep",
            "b": "being kept",
            "c": "keeping",
            "d": "to have kept",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "\n- Have /find + somebody/ time/money/ place/ energy/ chance/opportunity/ encourage... + To Verb",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "When a molar started to ache, I decided it was time ___ a dentist.",
            "a": "see",
            "b": "to see",
            "c": "to have seen",
            "d": "seeing",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- It's time to do something \n- It's time somebody did something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tennis champion has been asked ___ an exhibition game at the tennis club next Sunday.",
            "a": "play",
            "b": "to play",
            "c": "to be played",
            "d": "to have played",
            "answer": "2",
            "explain": "\n- Ask (somebody) to do something \n- Passive voice: be asked to do something",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "43",
            "subcategorylv2": "4",
            "type": "1"
        }
    ]
}